[
  {
    "theme": "task",
    "question": "close your eyes. third person to put their hand on their head wins.",
    "answer": null,
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "dad",
      "australian",
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "task",
    "question": "get a fruit/vegetable and draw a face on it. best face wins. you have 1 minute",
    "answer": null,
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "dad",
      "australian",
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "task",
    "question": "draw the best mexican flag. you have 30 seconds",
    "answer": null,
    "askers": [
      "hippy",
      "australian",
      "gapyear",
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "task",
    "question": "put on the most jumpers. you have 1 minute",
    "answer": null,
    "askers": [
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6",
      "australian",
      "gapyear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "task",
    "question": "I went to see some lovely waterfalls yesterday. Let's recreate them. Virtual waterfall!!",
    "answer": null,
    "askers": [
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6",
      "australian",
      "gapyear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "task",
    "question": "I went to see some lovely waterfalls yesterday. Let's recreate them. Virtual waterfall!!",
    "answer": null,
    "askers": [
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6",
      "australian",
      "gapyear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "task",
    "question": "I went to see some lovely waterfalls yesterday. Let's recreate them. Virtual waterfall!!",
    "answer": null,
    "askers": [
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6",
      "australian",
      "gapyear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "task",
    "question": "chug. (5 seconds)",
    "answer": null,
    "askers": [
      "lad6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "task",
    "isPermanent": true,
    "question": "i’m not here on holiday. i am a member of the Tequila Regulatory Council and responsible for monitoring tequila quality at a random sample of beach resorts. I’ve just arrived and am about to do an initial tasting - you should have some too!",
    "answer": null,
    "askers": [
      "bigtequila"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "what is the symbolism of a simnel cake?",
    "answer": "the eleven marzipan balls represent the eleven apostles of jesus excluding judas",
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "dad",
      "maga",
      "vicar1",
      "vicar2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "where did jesus go after the last supper?",
    "answer": "the garden of gethsemane",
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "dad",
      "maga",
      "vicar1",
      "vicar2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "the idea of the easter bunny originated in which country?",
    "answer": "germany",
    "askers": [
      "gapyear",
      "australian"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "in australia, we don’t have the easter bunny - do you know what we have instead?",
    "answer": "the easter bilby",
    "askers": [
      "australian"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "i saw this video on youtube, the End of the CABAL, guess who is going to replace donald trump to break the CABAL?",
    "answer": "jfk junior - everyone thinks he died in 1999 but he is going to use time travel to jump to a different timeline",
    "askers": [
      "maga"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "in millions, how many creme eggs are made each year?",
    "answer": "500 million",
    "askers": [
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3",
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2",
      "gapyear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "at easter, americans will eat enough jelly beans to go around the world three times - how many million jelly beans is that?",
    "answer": "16 million",
    "askers": [
      "maga",
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "when was the uk’s first chocolate egg made?",
    "answer": "1873",
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "dad",
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "what is the traditional easter game of pace-egging? ",
    "answer": "rolling hard-boiled eggs down a hill",
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "dad",
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3",
      "vicar1",
      "vicar2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "which musician has not recorded a song called Easter? a. Bruce Springsteen b. Jefferson Airplane c. Patti Smith",
    "answer": "a) Bruce Springsteen",
    "askers": [
      "hippy",
      "gapyear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "when was buying alcohol on good friday legalised in ireland?",
    "answer": "2018",
    "askers": [
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "could you tell me the best wine to pair with my Roasted Leg of Lamb with Fennel and Carrots?",
    "answer": "Pinot Noir - The hints of sour cherry complement both the roast and the accompanying spring vegetables.",
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "dad",
      "vicar1",
      "vicar2",
      "hippy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "tigerking",
    "question": "what were the two potential ways that carole baskin disposed of her second husband",
    "answer": "she fed him to the tigers or she buried him in the septic tank",
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "inflencer1",
      "inflencer2",
      "maga",
      "hippy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "tigerking",
    "question": "name one of joe exotic's songs",
    "answer": "one of ‘pretty woman lover’,‘how was i to know’,‘say something’,‘this is my life’,‘john finlay’,‘because you love me’,‘i saw a tiger’,‘here kitty kitty’",
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "dad",
      "maga",
      "hippy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "tigerking",
    "question": "what was the name of carole baskin's original wildlife park?",
    "answer": "wildlife on easy street",
    "askers": [
      "mum",
      "dad",
      "maga",
      "hippy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "easter",
    "question": "what is the official flower of easter?",
    "answer": "lillies - they represent grace and purity",
    "askers": [
      "hippy",
      "mum",
      "vicar1",
      "vicar2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "i’m making margaritas! what ingredients do i need?",
    "answer": "tequila, conintreau/orange liqueur, lime juice, salt",
    "askers": [
      "australian",
      "gapyear",
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6",
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "what is the difference between silver and gold tequila?",
    "answer": "silver tequila is bottled straight after distillation. gold tequila is matured for longer in barrels which gives it it’s colour",
    "askers": [
      "australian",
      "gapyear",
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "how many states does mexico have?",
    "answer": "31 states",
    "askers": [
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6",
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "as of 2017, to the nearest 1000, how many US born people were resident in mexico?",
    "answer": "899,311",
    "askers": [
      "maga",
      "hippy",
      "gapyear",
      "australian"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "the worlds smallest volcano, cuexcomate, is in mexico. how tall is it?",
    "answer": "43 feet /13m",
    "askers": [
      "hippy",
      "gapyear",
      "australian",
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3",
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6",
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "how many types of corn does mexico have?",
    "answer": "59",
    "askers": [
      "hippy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "who did the aztecs ban from eating avocados?",
    "answer": "virgins - avocados were thought to be too sexually powerful",
    "askers": [
      "hippy",
      "gapyear",
      "australian",
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "where does the word avocado come from?",
    "answer": "the aztec word for testicle",
    "askers": [
      "gapyear",
      "australian",
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "mexico is the world’s largest exporter of what? ",
    "answer": "beer ",
    "askers": [
      "gapyear",
      "australian",
      "lad1",
      "lad2",
      "lad3",
      "lad4",
      "lad5",
      "lad6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "what are the names of the couple from Love is Blind who went home after having a big argument on the first night in mexico?",
    "answer": "diamond and carlton",
    "askers": [
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "what are the ingredients of guacamole as per the G-U-A-C-A-M-O-L-E guacamole song?",
    "answer": "avocado, diced tomato, onions, chillis, garlic, salt, pepper, cilantro and a little lime juice to retain colour",
    "askers": [
      "gapyear",
      "australian",
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3",
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "in millions, how many dogs are there in mexico?",
    "answer": "23 million ",
    "askers": [
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3",
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "if the word mexico were allowed in scrabble, how many points would it get?",
    "answer": "17",
    "askers": [
      "vicar1",
      "vicar2",
      "mum",
      "dad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "theme": "mexico",
    "question": "name five flavours of the mexican soft drink Jarritos",
    "answer": "Hibiscus, Cola, Grapefruit, Mandarin, Tamarind, Strawberry, Lime, Guava, Fruit Punch, Pineapple, Mango, Watermelon, Lemon-Lime  ",
    "askers": [
      "kid1",
      "kid2",
      "kid3",
      "bartender",
      "influencer1",
      "influencer2"
    ]
  }
]